{
    "subject": "Comoros",
    "predicate": "hasOfficialLanguage",
    "object": "Comorian_language",
    "human_readable": "The Comoros has the official language Comorian.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8890160918235779,
            "question": "What is the official language of the Comoros?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8770738840103149,
            "question": "Is Comorian the primary language spoken in the Comoros?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8491124510765076,
            "question": "Besides Comorian, are there other languages spoken in the Comoros?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7293306589126587,
            "question": "What language group does Comorian belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6875491142272949,
            "question": "How does the official language influence culture in the Comoros?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6517996191978455,
            "question": "Can you provide some examples of words in the Comorian language?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6131796836853027,
            "question": "Are there any dialects of Comorian spoken in different regions of the country?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5757784843444824,
            "question": "What are some efforts being made to preserve and promote the Comorian language?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5737683176994324,
            "question": "What are the historical influences on the development of the Comorian language?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48826196789741516,
            "question": "How does the use of Comorian impact education and communication in the Comoros?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Comoros has the official language Comorian.",
            "html": "yago_26787_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are the historical influences on the development of the Comorian language?",
            "html": "yago_26787_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some efforts being made to preserve and promote the Comorian language?",
            "html": "yago_26787_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any dialects of Comorian spoken in different regions of the country?",
            "html": "yago_26787_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26787_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26787_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26787_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26787_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26787_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26787_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26787_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26787_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26787_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26787_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents support that Comorian is one of the official languages of the Comoros Islands, making the statement \"The Comoros has the official language Comorian\" correct."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}